<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MIMIc Project</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>MIMIc Project</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This project has received funding from the European Research Council (ERC) under the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme (Grant agreement No. 852317)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>MIMIc Project</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos</title>
      <link>/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/videos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;belgium-dr-laura-vandenbosch-university-of-leuven&#34;&gt;Belgium: Dr. Laura Vandenbosch (University of Leuven)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p4ZA5jjQJ3Q&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;slovenia-dr-bojana-lobe-university-of-ljubljana&#34;&gt;Slovenia: Dr. Bojana Lobe (University of Ljubljana)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6oRIBmtVwKc&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;france-dr-caroline-giraudeau-university-of-tours&#34;&gt;France: Dr. Caroline Giraudeau (University of Tours)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zkSEIChKRIU&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Parents</title>
      <link>/parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/parents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear sir/madam,
We are project MIMIc. Our goal is to broaden the understanding of what it means to grow up in a digital world. “Do youth mimic the lifestyles they encounter on their social media feeds and in entertainment fiction?” is a key question in this project and refers to learning which norms and beliefs youth adopt from interacting with media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We ask this question in hopes of helping youth, such as your child, better navigate the complexities of a digital society and make the most of their social media use. We aim to accomplish this goal by conducting three different studies amongst adolescents across Europe. Below you can find some more information on what these three studies entail. If you have any questions on the ethical measures undertaken by project MIMIc to ensure the wellbeing of every single participant, we would like to direct you to the “Adolescent” section on this website, or the digital information sheet accessible on the online platform of your child’s school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, the MIMic research team will first look at media that are popular among adolescents to understand the lifestyles that are promoted on these platforms. This research will study music lyrics (for instance the lyrics of Katy Perry or Drake), TV shows (for instance the popular series 13 Reasons Why), Instagram profiles of famous influencers (for instance the Kardashian family) and the Instagram and Snapchat profiles of adolescents. By looking at the subjects that characters in popular TV series talk about, the images that influencers post online and the posts that adolescents share in their social network we learn more about the subjects adolescents are confronted with when using media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, the MIMic research team will next follow a group of youngsters aged 12 to 16 years old over the course of one year to see what it’s like to grow-up in a media-filled world. Three countries (i.e., France, Slovenia and Belgium) take part in this ‘panel study’. More precisely, adolescents are asked at three different time points in 2020-2021 to answer a survey online at their home. Adolescents are invited to participate in the survey through their school. In the survey, we ask about adolescents’ media diets and how adolescents think about themselves, their peers, their body, school results and sexuality. With the answers that adolescents give to our questions we learn to understand how media interactions play a role in growing up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the MIMIc research team will monitor adolescents, surveying them daily, for a period of 14 days near the end of 2021. The participants in this diary research will be a subset from the pool of participants from the longitudinal research. More precisely, adolescents are asked to complete a diary in the shape of a brief survey online at their home. In this diary survey, we ask about how adolescents have spent their day and in particular focus on their daily media interactions. With this study we learn to understand why on some days youth benefit from spending time with media, while on other days their media interactions seem to be rather fatiguing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Participants</title>
      <link>/adolescents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/adolescents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
We - at team MIMIc - want to help youngsters, such as yourself, get the most out of their media use. What this means is that we are committed to learning which elements from your media use help you or make you happy, and which don’t. In order to gain a better understanding of these things, we want to see how you and your peers use media. If you, like us, are curious about how your experience with media can be improved, maybe we can help each other out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do we do?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
We are organizing research across three different countries (Belgium, Slovenia and France) as part of a European project led by Prof. L. Vandenbosch. We want to gain insights into the media that you and your friends like to use (12 to 17 year-old) and the type of content you often see. Our team aims to understand how adolescents, such as yourself, interact with these messages that appear on social media, television and in popular music lyrics, both over a long period of time and on a daily basis. We would also like to know if and how you post about yourself on social media (e.g., Instagram and TikTok). More generally, we would like to learn more about the relationship between your media use and how you and your peers think about yourselves, each other, your body, your school results and the world around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After our research, we would provide you and your school with a report. This report would include tips &amp;amp; tricks to help you manage specific difficulties that come with media. In that way, these reports will help you reap the most benefit from using these media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a token of appreciation for your participation in our study, you will be given an &lt;em&gt;individual gift voucher&lt;/em&gt; (increasing in value as you participate in more parts of the study). In addition, there will also be  lotteries to win additional vouchers. The tokens of appreciation are given based on the time you invest in the research. If you decide to revoke the use of your personal data after completing the research, the vouchers will still be given.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about data confidentiality (your privacy)?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Confidentiality of identifying data will always be guaranteed. In other words, we promise that the information you provide us will remain private. The obtained research results will be used for scientific research only, these scientific reports will never contain any identifying information (such as your name or birth date). The data are used in agreement with the law (GDPR) and the strict rules set by KU Leuven, University of Tours, University of Ljubljana. You can find more information on the procedures and the confidentiality of the research in information brochures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Practical information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Our project consists of multiple studies. Find more information about each of them below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Longitudinal Research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The Longitudinal Study is the largest study. Here, we will ask a large group (5,400) of students across Europe (Belgium, France &amp;amp; Slovenia) to participate. Taking part in this study is a requirement to be invited for any of the other studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you participate in our Longitudinal Study, you will be asked to complete a survey on how you interact with the media at three different time points over the course of one year. These surveys will always be the same, because we want to see if and how your opinion on these topics evolves over time. The survey contains questions about your body, the importance of your appearance, school results, beauty ideals, sexuality, your media use (for instance social media) and how you think about your peers and the world around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Diary Research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The Diary Study is smaller in scope than the previous one. Here we will only ask a total of 1,000 adolescents to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are invited to help us with the Diary Study, we will ask you to complete a brief survey at home on how you interact with the media, every evening before bed. This survey will always be the same, because we want to see how your daily experiences affect how you feel about certain things. Completing this survey will take approximately 10 minutes, and can be completed by using a computer, a phone or a tablet with internet connection. The survey contains questions about your body, the importance of your appearance, school results, beauty ideals, your media use (for instance social media) and how you think about your peers and the world around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Social Media Study&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The final study we will organize is a social media study. Just like the Diary Study, a smaller group of 1,000 adolescents will be asked to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are invited to participate in our Social Media Study, you will be asked to accept a friendship or follow request from a social media profile specifically designed for the current research. During the time of the data collection, the researchers will be part of your online network, similar to your other friends/followers on these networks. Next, the researchers will take screenshots to investigate the pictures, status updates and messages you post on your social media profiles. Only the researchers have access to the screenshots and will investigate them by calculating, for instance, the number of pictures on a profile before deleting these screenshots permanently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results of the research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you participate in our research, you will receive a report presenting the most important results of the study every six months after the data collection has taken place. These reports will include the findings of the research, but also tips and tricks on how you can optimize your media interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance for your cooperation, your help is greatly appreciated. Any questions? You can always 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.projectmimic.eu/contact/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; the responsible researcher in your country.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Literate Schools</title>
      <link>/media_lit_schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/media_lit_schools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This research is only made possible thanks to the participation of wonderful Media Literate Schools across Belgium, France &amp;amp; Slovenia. These media literate schools chose to expend considerable effort to help further the understanding of media effects on adolescents in Europe. We are thankful for their cooperation and commitment to helping adolescents gain the most out of their media use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As token of our gratitude, these schools will receive a digital literacy training package at the end of Project MIMIc. This package will contain a report about the research results, two digital video clips and a discussion guide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first digital video clip is targeted at adolescents and explains the results of the research and their implications for the lives of adolescents. Schools are highly supported to motivate teachers and pupils to watch the video clip together and have a discussion about the results afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To train teachers into experienced moderators for discussions about media literacy skills, a second digital video clip is targeted at teachers and explains them the core attention points that have to be taken into account when moderating classroom discussions about the results of the research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To organize the discussion, the discussion guide contains a detailed step-wise explanation on how a conversation can unfold and presents several subjects to discuss in class. Schools who implement the digital literacy training package in their curriculum are invited to also ask students to complete a brief survey before and after the training. This survey is analysed by the MIMIc Team and gives the school feedback on the training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As such, schools that participate in Project MIMIc and make use of the digital literacy training package provided, can truly consider themselves a &lt;em&gt;Media Literate School&lt;/em&gt;. Fully equipped to help students navigate the complexities of an increasingly digital society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find a list of these helpful Media Literate Schools, 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.projectmimic.eu/list/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Science</title>
      <link>/open_science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/open_science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Quickly discover relevant content by &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/&#34;&gt;filtering publications&lt;/a&gt;.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools</title>
      <link>/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[insert here school list]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;organization-of-the-research&#34;&gt;Organization of the research&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions about the organization of the research, you can always contact the responsible researcher in each country:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brent Swinnen&lt;/strong&gt; for all &lt;em&gt;Belgian&lt;/em&gt; related research questions:&lt;br&gt;
• tel: +32 16 37 39 64,&lt;br&gt;
• email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mimic.belgium@kuleuven.be&#34;&gt;mimic.belgium@kuleuven.be&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
• 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kuleuven.be/wieiswie/en/person/00113344&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anaelle Gonzalez&lt;/strong&gt; for all &lt;em&gt;French&lt;/em&gt; related research questions:&lt;br&gt;
• tel: +32 16 19 37 89,&lt;br&gt;
• email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mimic.france@kuleuven.be&#34;&gt;mimic.france@kuleuven.be&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
• 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kuleuven.be/wieiswie/en/person/00136069&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jasmina Rosic&lt;/strong&gt; for all &lt;em&gt;Slovenian&lt;/em&gt; related research questions:&lt;br&gt;
• tel: +32 16 19 47 48,&lt;br&gt;
• email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mimic.slovenia@kuleuven.be&#34;&gt;mimic.slovenia@kuleuven.be&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
• 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kuleuven.be/wieiswie/en/person/00142166&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For research about the &lt;em&gt;overall framework&lt;/em&gt;, you can address the principal investigator, Prof. &lt;strong&gt;Laura Vandenbosch&lt;/strong&gt;. She is the Principal Investigator of the ERC starting grant project (code MIMIc, nr 852317):&lt;br&gt;
• tel: +32 16 32 32 02,&lt;br&gt;
• email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:laura.vandenbosch@kuleuven.be&#34;&gt;laura.vandenbosch@kuleuven.be&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;
• 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kuleuven.be/wieiswie/en/person/00060068&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ethical-procedures&#34;&gt;Ethical procedures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions about the ethical procedures of the research, we would like to inform you that this study is approved by the &lt;strong&gt;Ethical Commission of Social and Human Sciences of the Catholic University of Leuven&lt;/strong&gt; (SMEC), &lt;strong&gt;CER Tours-Poitiers – Courriel of the University of Tours&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;ethical board of the University Ljubljana&lt;/strong&gt;.
Questions regarding the approved ethical guidelines can be emailed to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:SMEC@kuleuven.be&#34;&gt;SMEC@kuleuven.be&lt;/a&gt; (for Belgium)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:presidencecertp@univ-tours.fr&#34;&gt;presidencecertp@univ-tours.fr&lt;/a&gt; (for France)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Bojana.Lobe@fdv.uni-lj.si&#34;&gt;Bojana.Lobe@fdv.uni-lj.si&lt;/a&gt; (for Slovenia)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, an additional ethical board has been constituted to monitor the ethical guidelines applied in the current study and consists out of Prof. &lt;strong&gt;Eva Lievens&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:E.Lievens@UGent.be&#34;&gt;E.Lievens@UGent.be&lt;/a&gt;), Prof. &lt;strong&gt;Moniek Buijzen&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:m.buijzen@ru.nl&#34;&gt;m.buijzen@ru.nl&lt;/a&gt;), Prof. &lt;strong&gt;Drew Cingel&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dcingel@ucdavis.edu&#34;&gt;dcingel@ucdavis.edu&lt;/a&gt;) and Dr. &lt;strong&gt;Sandra Verbeken&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sandra.Verbeken@UGent.be&#34;&gt;Sandra.Verbeken@UGent.be&lt;/a&gt;) will further confidentially monitor the approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;processig-of-personal-data&#34;&gt;Processig of personal data&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions about the processing of personal data, please contact:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the &lt;strong&gt;Data Protection Officer of KU Leuven&lt;/strong&gt; via &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dpo@kuleuven.be&#34;&gt;dpo@kuleuven.be&lt;/a&gt; (for Belgium)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the &lt;strong&gt;Data Protection Officer of University of Tours&lt;/strong&gt; via &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:daj@univ-tours.fr&#34;&gt;daj@univ-tours.fr&lt;/a&gt; (for France)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the &lt;strong&gt;Data Protection Officer of University of Ljubljana&lt;/strong&gt; via &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:dpo@uni-lj.si&#34;&gt;dpo@uni-lj.si&lt;/a&gt; (for Slovenia)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Malleability Narrative in Entertainment and Social Media. Explaining Pathways to Happiness in Media Content.</title>
      <link>/publication/mimic_lv-se_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/mimic_lv-se_2020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/data_confidentiality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/data_confidentiality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The MIMIc research has been approved by the ethical committees of the KU Leuven, U of Tours and U of Ljubljana. An ethical board monitors the ethical guidelines in the project. Confidentiality of identifying data is guaranteed. The obtained research results will be used for scientific research only, these scientific reports will never contain any identifying information (such as your child’s name or birth date). The data are used in agreement with the law (GDPR) and the strict KU Leuven, University De Tours, University of Ljubljana rules. Parents and participating adolescents can find more information on the procedures and the confidentiality of the research in information brochures. Adolescents can only participate in the research after parental approval. For more information, please 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.projectmimic.eu/en/contact/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; the responsible researcher in your country.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information Collection And Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
This website does not require you to identify yourself. The only personal information collected while you visit this site is non-identifying information, such as browser type and operating system. This information is collected by Google Analytics for measuring visitor traffic to this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not collect this information and have no access to it other than as aggregated reports. 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is the Google Analytics privacy page. In order to anonymize this process, we have set the Hugo GDPR options so that your IP address is anonymised within Google Analytics and the “Do Not Track” request is respected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For each visitor to reach the site, Google Analytics collects the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the site, page access times and referring website address. This information is presented to us as aggregated reports for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic and trends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
This information is collected via cookies. Most web browsers allow you to control handling of cookies. It is possible to disable all cookies for this website without in any way reducing the functionality for the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more about cookies, please refer to this 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cookiesandyou.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes To This Privacy Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 01 May 2020 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
