<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | MIMIc</title>
    <link>/sl/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/sl/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>sl</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/sl/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>admin</title>
      <link>/sl/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sl/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/sl/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sl/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sl/authors/admin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sl/authors/admin1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting from 2017, Laura Vandenbosch is an assistant professor at the School for Mass Communication Research (BOF-ZAP research professorship grant). The relationship between media and well-being is the core subject of her research, leading to international publications in several fields including developmental psychology, sexology, body image, social relationships and communication theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2015 she was elected as the secretary of the Children, Adolescents and Media Division of the International Communication Association (2015-2018). Laura is currently also an editorial board member of ISI-ranked journals Human Communication Research, Journal of Children and Media, and Communications: The European Journal of Communication Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, she is involved in several (international) research projects aimed to study how media may affect well-being by focusing on factors that have not been understood well, such as the role of social relationships, cultural background, sexualization, media literacy and malleability beliefs. Part of these projects are embedded within the international network she has built throughout the years by spending periods abroad at, for instance, the U of Michigan, the U of Toronto and the U of Vienna. Her work has led to several awards, such as the Top Paper, Top Article and Top Dissertation Awards from the Children, Adolescents and Media (CAM) Division of the International Communication Association (2013-2016) and the Research Council Award in the Humanities (Prijs Onderzoeksraad, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2019, she received an ERC starting grant for the project “Malleability in mediated ideals: A paradigm to understand effects of contemporary media in adolescents’ well-being.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sl/authors/admin2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sl/authors/admin2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anaëlle Gonzalez is a PhD student at the Leuven School for Mass Communication Research (KU Leuven) under supervision of Professor Laura Vandenbosch. Her PhD project focuses on Adolescents’ Media Diets, the Individualistic Discourse et Political beliefs and Participation. It is part of the bigger ERC starting grant on Malleable Mediated Ideals and adolescents’ wellbeing. This project uses a multidisciplinary approach as it combines communication science, cultural sociology and psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sl/authors/admin3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sl/authors/admin3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Brent Swinnen is a PhD student at the Leuven School for Mass Communication. He’s currently working under supervision of Professor Laura Vandenbosch on the ERC-funded project: “Malleability in mediated ideals: A paradigm to understand effects of contemporary media in adolescents’ well-being”. His PhD project specifically pertains to the notions of malleability, performance pressure and well-being amongst adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sl/authors/admin4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sl/authors/admin4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am PhD candidate at the School for Mass Communication Research, KU Leuven (BE). My research interests lie at the intersection of media effects, cultural and cognitive sociology. I employ dual-process models of cognition to study how media shape perceptions of inequalities about gender, class, and race and to understand the enculturation process behind this transmission.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
