<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | MIMIc Project</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This project has received funding from the European Research Council (ERC) under the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme (Grant agreement No. 852317)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Vandenbosch</title>
      <link>/authors/laura-vandenbosch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/laura-vandenbosch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Eggermont</title>
      <link>/authors/steven-eggermont/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/steven-eggermont/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/1admin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/1admin1/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Starting from 2017, Laura Vandenbosch is an assistant professor at the School for Mass Communication Research (BOF-ZAP research professorship grant). The relationship between media and well-being is the core subject of her research, leading to international publications in several fields including developmental psychology, sexology, body image, social relationships and communication theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2015 she was elected as the secretary of the Children, Adolescents and Media Division of the International Communication Association (2015-2018). Laura is currently also an editorial board member of ISI-ranked journals Human Communication Research, Journal of Children and Media, and Communications: The European Journal of Communication Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, she is involved in several (international) research projects aimed to study how media may affect well-being by focusing on factors that have not been understood well, such as the role of social relationships, cultural background, sexualization, media literacy and malleability beliefs. Part of these projects are embedded within the international network she has built throughout the years by spending periods abroad at, for instance, the U of Michigan, the U of Toronto and the U of Vienna. Her work has led to several awards, such as the Top Paper, Top Article and Top Dissertation Awards from the Children, Adolescents and Media (CAM) Division of the International Communication Association (2013-2016) and the Research Council Award in the Humanities (Prijs Onderzoeksraad, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2019, she received an ERC starting grant for the project “Malleability in mediated ideals: A paradigm to understand effects of contemporary media in adolescents’ well-being.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video width=&#34;320&#34; height=&#34;240&#34; controls&gt;
&lt;source src=&#34;LV.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/1admin2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/1admin2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anaëlle Gonzalez is a PhD student at the Leuven School for Mass Communication Research (KU Leuven) under supervision of Professor Laura Vandenbosch. Her PhD project focuses on Adolescents’ Media Diets, the Individualistic Discourse et Political beliefs and Participation. It is part of the bigger ERC starting grant on Malleable Mediated Ideals and adolescents’ wellbeing. This project uses a multidisciplinary approach as it combines communication science, cultural sociology and psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/1admin3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/1admin3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Brent Swinnen is a PhD student at the Leuven School for Mass Communication. He’s currently working under supervision of Professor Laura Vandenbosch on the ERC-funded project: “Malleability in mediated ideals: A paradigm to understand effects of contemporary media in adolescents’ well-being”. His PhD project specifically pertains to the notions of malleability, performance pressure and well-being amongst adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/1admin4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/1admin4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a PhD student at the School for Mass Communication Research, KU Leuven (BE). My research interests lie at the intersection of cultural and cognitive sociology, media effects research, and the study of inequalities.
From a theoretical point of view, I study how socialization processes among adolescents might shape the formation of their beliefs about inequalities. Drawing from cultural sociology, I study how the socially-stratified access and engagement with prestigious symbolic goods (i.e., music genres) might act as a form of cultural differentiation. Drawing from the media effects literature, I study how music portrays social status and the possible routes through which these portrayals influence adolescents beliefs.
Empirically, I employ quantitative methodologies, such as social network analysis, structural equation modelling, and computational text analysis. I am committed to an open science framework and mindset.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/4clb_user10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/4clb_user10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/4clb_user11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/4clb_user11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Caroline Giraudeau is a lecturer at the Department of Psychology (University of Tours, France). She is interested in the relationships between adolescents and young adults and their grandparents, and more particularly in the emotional closeness between them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, she is involved in several (international) research projects on student-teacher relationships (with the University of Kentucky), a multinational study on emotional traits and relational and psychological health (e.g., stress, depression, self-esteem) (with the University of Arizona), and a cross-cultural study on the relationships and expectations of grandparents and young adults (with Penn State Hazleton University).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has two interests in the MIMIc project concerning the French participants: What photos and texts do teenagers share about their grandparents in social networks? Friendship during adolescence in social networks: What experience(s) of emotional closeness do French adolescents have with their peers and with celebrities?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
